The 1900s are almost over,
and the new millennium's
about to arrive...
I'm kind of hoping
society collapses. Work sucks!
No, no, no, we're all
just going to get shit-faced.
This morning,
staff have been standing by
to handle bug related problems
as midnight strikes...
There's a Y2K problem
and nobody's saying
what's going on...
fly to Perth,
but darling,
I am frightened
of the big Y2K bug...
It's a hoax!
I just hope
I get a new year's pash...
A couple of wild
cards from the North Shore,
and what are you girls
getting up to tonight?
It's New Year's Eve!
Whoa!
Oh mate, it's a beat up.
I just wanna get smashed.
Slip, slop, smashed.
There's still a few
hours to go until midnight.
We're counting down the
top hits of the nineties.
I'm sure you all know this one.
Hi there. My name is
Dr. Minnie Vernon.
Can you please tell me your
name and your date of birth?
Can you please confirm your
And what operation
are you having today?
Good...
I am never doing this again.
Hi Lucy. How you doing?
My name's Dr. Minnie Vernon.
I'm an anaesthetist.
I understand you'd like
an epidural today.
Oh, give me the drugs!
Lucy, I think if you just give
it a little bit more time.
Well, it's really just
about what you want, Lucy.
I'm here to help you out.
So would you like the epidural?
- Yes. Thank you.
- Great.
Um, so let me explain
that procedure to you.
It's just an injection
in your back.
It's the size of a hair...
Why are you eating a sandwich?
Where's my apple juice?
It's been hours,
I was about to faint.
Fine! I'll go back for it.
- Minnie.
- Cameron.
You know her?
Yeah, Minnie and I
are old friends.
- Cam and I were engaged.
- Oh my God!
Ronny, is this the ex?
Hey Lucy, look at me.
You don't need drugs, okay?
So Ronny, a baby?
Congratulations.
It's funny though
because we kind of broke up
because you said
you didn't want kids.
We broke up because
you kind of slept
with your best mate, Joe.
Keep breathing.
Okay, but you did say that you
didn't want kids, didn't you?
I didn't want kids, then!
Okay. We broke up
like six months ago, so...
What?
It was two years ago.
Tell her.
Oh, wow.
Oh yeah. No, he's right.
It was definitely two years ago.
Time flies, hey?
Still though,
I'm pretty sure you said
- you never wanted kids.
- With you.
It's coming.
Do I lie down now?
Gotcha.
No, no,
we keep standing and Lucy
we're going to bear down
like a coffee plunger, okay?
You're doing amazing, babe.
That's it.
Keep breathing.
- Okay, so Lucy, just a couple...
- Get out!
Yes, absolutely.
Min!
Why aren't you dressed?
Um, I'm not coming.
- What? You have to come?
- I'm really tired.
I had a long shift and
it's just going to be
a bunch of boring
couples anyway.
Ah, it is an intimate gathering
of some of your closest friends
who would all love to see you.
Besides, Rodney wants
to have a big one.
Yeah, nah. I'm just going to
stay on the couch. Sorry.
You know, a fold-up couch
is actually supposed
to fold back up.
Oh, good.
We're having the conversation.
What conversation?
The "you leaving" conversation.
Are you kicking me out?
Minnie, I know that things
have been hard
since Cameron dumped you
and Joe left.
Yeah...
- But Max and I...
- We want the room back.
Oh, that's Rodney.
Better get that.
Tell him I'm not coming.
One second.
Hey.
G'day, we need you to bring
some ice, like four bags.
Pia!
Hey, Mum and Dad are here.
Where's the monitor?
- The monitor?
- Baby, let's go...
I dunno. I think
I left it in Joe's room.
- Does she need it?
- Yeah.
Sorry, baby's first night away.
- Did you just say Joe's room?
- Oh, shit.
Is Joe back?
Yeah, he got in this morning.
Joe's back. Put him on.
Yay.
He's asleep. Look,
I didn't say anything, okay?
- He wants to surprise you.
- Okay.
- Minnie's not coming.
- You have to come.
I'm turning the clock
back tonight.
Rodney is off the leash.
I am, don't worry.
I'm definitely coming.
- Okay.
- Hey, Rodney.
- Yeah,
- They're leaving.
- Okay.
- Are you saying bye?
Yep, be there in a second.
Thank you. Okay.
- Okay. Don't forget the ice.
- Yep. Bye.
♪ I'm heading out where
the water is much deeper ♪
♪ I save myself
I'm saving you ♪
♪ I'm heading out I'm going
there and I'm gonna make it ♪
♪ I save myself
I'm saving you ♪
- You know it's a costume party?
- Yeah.
- So what are you going as?
- Ah, I'm going as 'Friends'.
- Oh, which one?
- All of them.
Perfect.
Oh great, you're
finally going to drink that?
No, it's a gift for Joe.
Oh, no.
It's a gift for you, from me.
I got it in Mexico for you
10 years ago.
Oh shit.
Do you think tequila goes off?
Probably, hey?
Hey, after what happened
at the hospital today,
I don't want you to do
anything rash.
Oh, Flick, it's going
to be fine. Okay?
We're just going to,
going to have a few drinks
and see where the
night takes us.
Well the night usually takes
you and Joe to Bang Town.
Here we go. This will do.
Party time.
- Do you need to wee?
- No, Mum.
♪ You're the reason
why I chose to stay ♪
♪ It's been a long time ♪
♪ To find your dream
and hold on to it ♪
♪ All I needed was to fly ♪
♪ It's a long way from
innocence to understanding ♪
♪ Picture of a child at play
is how I feel today ♪
♪ And I remember ♪
♪ How it all came true
By the sweet Sorrento moon ♪
Ah, you didn't tell me
Rodney was loaded.
Yeah, somehow he always managed
to fall ass backwards into...
Oh, look at the water feature.
I need to wee.
Hey, try not to fall on Joe's
dick before we get inside, yeah?
What time is it?
You know what time it is.
Party time!
- Rodney told you, didn't he?
- Yeah. Yes, he did.
Wait, who are you
supposed to be?
Um...
Nineties legend - Minnie Vernon?
Nice of you to make the effort.
Yeah well, who are you
supposed to be? A bag of dicks?
Yeah.
Jeez. You don't
waste any time.
It's party time. Get on it.
No, I can't.
I think I'm allergic
- To tequila?
- Mm.
- New York's changed you, mate.
- It has actually.
You know, just before we go in...
Alrighty then!
Hey...
What's going on? All good?
Good...
What's ah -
where's your costume?
I didn't have time.
Does it matter?
No, it's just silliness,
isn't it?
Bring the ice?
I didn't, sorry.
Perfect. Um...
Well thanks for coming, mate.
Is this yours?
Yes. Weird.
Yeah. Come in.
I want to show you something.
Okay.
Rodney, where's the ice?
Minnie! I didn't think
that you were coming.
Hey Pia, long time no see.
Yes! We missed you
at the birthday.
Oh, sorry. I thought
it was a kid's party.
It was...
Our kid's birthday party.
Have a Sea Breeze. They just,
they just need some ice.
Have you told Minnie
about the, the flight path?
- He thinks I'm overreacting.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Everyone should know.
So, when Y2K shuts down
all the computers...
- If!
- When!
Planes will literally
start falling from the sky.
I mean, what do I know?
I just work in IT.
- Well, worked in IT.
- And you're a real doctor.
Okay...
Hey, do you think they
know that I'm The Nanny?
Ta-dah!
- Ah, 'Dumb and Dumber'?
- Oh...
Kurt Cobain.
Baby Frances.
Yes!
- Hey.
- Hi.
Here, hold that.
Hello, you look great.
Thank you.
Can you pick it?
Hmm?
Hey, you should have
told me about your costume.
I could've come as Courtney.
Isn't Jenny coming
as Courtney Cox.
- Love.
- Huh?
It's Love.
Sorry, who's Jenny?
Who's Jenny?
- You look good.
- So do you.
Are you sure that it's Love?
Sure looks like it.
Guys. Guys, this is Jenny.
This is Max and Flick
and Minnie.
Wow. I have heard so
much about you.
Really? It's funny, I haven't
heard anything about you.
Ah, surprise.
We met at a bar.
- Didn't we?
- This guy, my worst tipper.
No, to be fair,
tipping's not really
a thing here in Australia.
You worked a bar?
You're a bar chick?
Mixologist.
I'm actually kinda
taking a break right now.
I'm in-between careers.
A bit of a dilettante.
I'm not sure
that's the right word.
Oh my God, she's not breathing.
Does anyone know a doctor?
She's good.
I'm going to get
another Sea Breeze.
Does anyone want one?
- Let's get a photo of you three.
- Oh...
I don't know if I'm quite
ready for a photo yet.
Okay. That's fine.
Min, you want to pop out.
Alright. Beautiful.
Never mind.
You see, the album was called...
Need to wee.
Hey Pia, where's the toilet?
It's in the bathroom.
Uh, ocupado.
Um, I'd offer you a line,
but I'm almost out.
Sorry. Do you mind?
No, no, I don't mind.
I've seen it all before.
I'm an OB-GYN.
Okay. So...
Did you come
straight from work or?
What?
Isn't it obvious?
'ER'.
I'm George Clooney.
I haven't watched it.
Rodney and I share an office.
I'm Karl. Karl Siewert.
C-word?
S-I-E-W-E-R-T.
Ah, okay.
You're Doctor C-word
gynaecologist?
Correct.
And you are?
I'm Minnie.
Like the mouse.
Yeah.
Can I get some privacy?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Hey ah, so Minnie,
Rodney tells me you're single.
Oh, does he?
That's great. Thanks Rodney.
You have a massive bit
of parsley in your teeth.
Is it really bothering you?
I, I mean, I guess not.
If it bothers you,
I can move it.
No, that's okay.
Shall we?
Being safe is better than
being sorry. Generally.
Yeah, exactly.
Like my friend in Miami.
They built a bunker, which
I feel is a bit much, but...
Come on. I, I think Y2K
is a massive beat up.
- I agree.
- Thank you, Joe.
I'm sorry.
Hey Jenny,
you should come with me.
I want to show you something.
Okay.
Don't worry, Joe.
I will bring her back.
Speaking of midnight,
guess what I got?
- Drugs?
- Fireworks.
- That's, that's still cool.
- Yeah. Okay.
But does anyone
have any drugs or...
So where did you two meet?
Met in the bathroom.
Ah, not on purpose.
- The bathroom?
- Classy.
- Maybe it's fate.
- It's not fate.
Oh my God,
you guys know the rules.
No wait. What's going on?
It's this stupid...
It started in uni, right?
We made up this stupid dance
and then every time
the song comes on,
we have to do the dance.
Like, one time Rodney
brought like a boombox
into an exam room.
- Yeah, that sounds lame.
- It's actually amazing.
Excuse me.
♪ Put me up, put me down, put
my feet back on the ground ♪
No!
♪ Feel my heart
and make me happy ♪
♪ Here we go
getting smooth to the groove ♪
♪ Watchin' lovely ladies
as I smooth as I move ♪
♪ 'Cause that's what they say
but I can't prove ♪
♪ So turn it up again and watch
me move to the groove ♪
♪ As we get close
you whisper, "Coco" ♪
♪ I hold you in my arms
and you say, "Jamboo" ♪
♪ Scream and shout,
turn and say "Colombo" ♪
♪ Now I gotta go, so coco ♪
♪ Put me up, put me down, put
my feet back on the ground ♪
♪ Put me up, take my heart
and make me happy ♪
- Okay! You need lessons, or?
- I got it.
Are you sure?
♪ Put me up, put me down, put
my feet back on the ground ♪
- So does it just start again?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You ready?
- Yep.
♪ Yeah-yeah-yeah, Coco Jamboo,
yeah-yeah-yeah ♪
Oh my, God! Jenny!
Whoa.
You're amazing.
- Yeah, she used to be a dancer.
- Still am baby.
Did she?
"Used to be a dancer".
Definitely code for stripper.
What's wrong with
being a stripper?
Well, now she's like an
unemployed bar chick.
Mixologist.
- Shut up.
- What?
He's not your boyfriend.
Max is right.
I know you were hoping for
something more with Joe,
but he has a girlfriend now
and she actually
seems really cool.
Yeah.
Wow.
You too, Brutus?
Whoa.
Talk about a sliding doors
moment.
- Minnie!
- Oh, is it bad?
- Rodney, do you have any ice?
- Ah, no.
Oh, wow. Farm picked.
I don't care about the peas.
All we're saying is
just give peas a chance.
Oh, my God.
That is not funny. Help me.
Alright. Alright.
Ow!
- You alright?
- Yeah.
Okay.
You want to take over?
- Yeah.
- How's your head?
I'm good. I'm good.
It's bad. It's bad.
- Hey, are you pissed?
- What?
With me, I mean about Jenny.
You know, I wanted to give
you a heads up at the door.
Um...
I want you to like her.
Right... Well...
Ah...
If you like her, I like her.
I love her.
- What?
- Hm-mm.
How long have you
even known each other?
- A few weeks.
- What?
I'm joking.
A few months.
Still, very quick.
Yeah, that's exactly what
her parents thought, but...
Her parents, you've,
you've met her parents?
You never even got
to meet my mum.
I have missed you, you know.
Does um, does Jenny
know about party time?
Yeah, she knows.
- Not a huge fan of the design.
- Okay...
But like, does she
know about us?
Yeah, she knows the gist.
She's cool.
Okay.
- Cool?
- Cool.
It's weird, isn't it?
It's like...
you never know it's
going to be the last time.
Like, at the time.
No, no, no, no.
I shouldn't do that.
Um...
- I can't.
- Yeah.
Um...
- Cool.
- Shit.
You know what?
I think my nose is fine.
No, no, hey Minnie...
No, no, it's fine.
Just forget it. Forget it.
Minnie?
You kissed?
No! Okay, okay, we kissed and
then we went skinny dipping.
- Right.
- I mean, you know,
Rodney was the first to get
naked and then stay naked
for the rest of the night.
- He was 'Living La Vida Loca'.
- Always.
It was like 10 years ago
and we took mushrooms.
And what happens in Mexico,
stays in Mexico.
Careful, baby.
- Fuck yeah!
- Truly exquisite.
- Do you want one?
- Who'd you kiss, Minnie?
What? No, Minnie
didn't come to Mexico.
- Oh...
- I didn't.
Just me, Rodney and Flick.
I just don't ever want to see
Rodney's balls again?
Amen.
- Where is Rodney?
- Fireworks, maybe.
- Oh guys, one minute.
- Okay.
A hundred billion dollars the
US spent trying to fix Y2K.
It's the biggest peace time
catastrophe in history.
And all for what?
For like two fucking digits.
I mean, you can't
avoid the inevitable.
The universe is always going to
find a way to course correct.
- Okay guys, 10 seconds.
- Happy apocalypse.
Maybe we should head to the
beach in case something happens.
No, it's going
to be great. I promise.
Alright, alright, alright.
10, 9, 8, 7,
6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- Happy new year!
- Hey...
It's happening.
Oh, cool...
It's okay...
Rodney?
It's the end of the world!
What?
That's funny.
- That's good. That's good.
- What is wrong with you?
Ah, where's the fucking
fireworks, Rodney?
Oh, my God.
- Um...
- Um?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yes, of course.
- Yes?
Oh wow. Okay.
- Yeah, that's a yes.
- Congrats!
I'm sorry, what?
Hey, this is mad.
Amazing.
♪ I'm like a waterlogged ball ♪
♪ That no-one wants
to kick around anymore ♪
♪ An all day morning hair-do
That no comb can get through ♪
♪ It's all granola and beer ♪
♪ And a calling card
and a silk cut souvenir ♪
♪ I miss you like sleep ♪
♪ And there's nothing romantic
about the hours I keep ♪
♪ The mornings when it starts
I don't look so sharp ♪
♪ Now I've got a heavy heart ♪
Huh.
What time is it?
It's, like, five past midnight.
I...
Rodney told you, didn't he?
This yours?
Yeah.
Is my nose okay?
What! Yeah, why?
Did you get a nose job?
No.
You got a nose job?
You didn't ask me to do it.
- No, I didn't get a nose job.
- I mean...
Actually, they didn't
do a terrible job.
Few things I'd do differently.
I broke my nose on the door.
Do you not remember?
Oh, hey, did you guys...
Rodney, where is the ice?
Minnie, hi, I, I didn't
think you were coming.
Have a Sea Breeze. There's
real cranberry vodka in them.
- They need ice.
- I know.
Rodney, where...
Hey, Pia, did you tell, uh, Min
about the, uh, the flight path?
- He thinks I'm overreacting.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Everyone should know,
so we're under a flight path.
- Yes, we are.
- And Pia tells me that when...
It's not completely certain.
When Y2K shuts down
all the computers...
Planes are going to start
falling out of the sky.
- She knows, too,
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- What do I know?
- I just work in IT.
- She just works in IT.
Correct, she's so
much smarter than you.
Worked in IT.
- I need to wee.
- Can you hold these?
- Ocupado?
- Oh, for fuck's sake.
Okay, look, you
can have one line.
Just keep it to yourself,
all right?
Can you please just let me wee?
Hey, fire away,
I've seen it all before.
I'm Karl, by the way.
Yes, C-word, I know.
We met.
- Uh, have we?
- Yeah.
Ria's birthday party.
Who the hell is Ria?
- Rodney and Pia's kid.
- Oh.
Okay, uh, whatever, can you,
can you leave, please?
Yeah, sure.
As in like get out.
Uh, just, oh, yeah,
give me one sec.
Bye.
That's enough. Out you go.
Oh, my God.
Oh, hey, Minnie,
Minnie, I want you to meet...
- Hi.
- Jenny.
I've heard so much about you.
Come here.
That was a little bit rude.
Um, I think I'm having
an aneurysm.
- What?
- Yeah.
Okay, well,
your pupils look fine.
- Do you have blurred vision?
- Nuh-uh.
Do you have a headache,
any pain?
No.
Well, so what are the symptoms?
Just like a, like, a
really intense déjà vu.
So what are the symptoms?
That's not funny.
What specifically is happening?
Okay, so it's like we got here,
yeah?
And we did the whole night,
and then it got to midnight,
and then everything
just started again.
Are you self-medicating again?
What? No, no, I'm not.
My God - Y2K.
It's Y2K. Pia!
I brought all our bank
statements just to be safe.
Like, I know it's going
to be fine, but...
But what if it's not?
Rodney thinks
that I'm overreacting.
- Hey, Pia.
- What?
Hey, what happened, Minnie?
Go, go, go, important.
What's the matter, Minnie?
- Pia?
- Yes.
You're right, Y2K. It's real.
Something's going to
happen at midnight.
- Yes.
- Minnie.
- Mm.
Don't worry. Y2K compliance,
it's my job.
- Okay.
- I code C++.
- Hold this.
- Yeah.
I have all the essentials.
- Okay.
- You're okay.
See, Minnie?
$1,986,173.
It is our entire life savings.
If anything was to happen,
we would all be able
to ride it out.
That's, um, well, um...
I just, uh, I don't actually
think it works like that.
What do you mean?
Well, it's like, okay...
So Y2K, I don't think
it's a bug, or a glitch,
or, like, a computer thing,
right?
It's, um, I don't even
know how to explain this.
It's, um, okay, uh...
Pia, I'm from the future.
Sure you are.
Pia, I'm serious, and I
kind of need your help.
You know, Rodney used
to take me seriously.
You remember that, don't you?
He doesn't anymore.
And I don't appreciate you
joining in on his fun and games.
Okay...
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
Happy New Year.
It's the end of the world!
Uh, where's the fucking
fireworks, Rodney?
No, seriously,
what is wrong with you?
I don't know.
I thought, like,
you'd be happy,
like you were right.
It's just a joke. Remember, you
used to love that kind of stuff.
I don't really see how all of
your friends laughing at me
is very funny.
Okay, between you and Minnie...
Sorry, what?
What about Minnie?
Do not pretend you
didn't put her up to it.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Really?
A time traveller visiting us
all the way from the year 2000.
I know it's you.
- What time is it?
- Oh, my God.
This yours?
Oh, Rodney told you, didn't he?
What time is it?
Okay.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, where
did you get this tequila?
Uh, I told you, Mexico.
Yeah, yeah, but, like,
where specifically,
some kind of Aztec shaman
or something?
I don't know, supermarket,
duty free. Why?
Just it's giving me some
very strange side effects.
Cool.
Do you know what this is?
Uh, no, but Rodney
knows Spanish. Ask him.
Orina del Diablo -
The Devil's Piss.
What does the rest of it say?
What, what's the worm saying?
Yeah, I don't know.
That's all the Spanish I know.
Also, fun fact, if it has a
worm in it, it's not tequila.
- It's mezcal.
- It's not a fun fact.
And if you eat the worm,
don't you get super wasted?
No, that's just a
marketing gimmick,
though the worm does
give it a distinctive taste.
- May I try some?
- No, you may not.
- Is everything okay, Minnie?
- Yeah.
Uh, Minnie, this yours?
Hello, is this yours?
Yeah.
Geez, why don't you
kiss already?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, I can't.
Oh, girl,
I wasn't being serious.
You're right.
You're so right.
Um, we should talk first,
reminisce, have a moment,
let it happen organically
like it was before.
No, no, I have a girlfriend.
Yeah, I know.
So that can't happen anymore.
Mm, I think it can.
Minnie, what is wrong with you?
No, no, he tried to
kiss me, before.
Trust me. There's still
something there.
Don't worry about it.
Ah, she's had a
really rough day.
No, I haven't had a rough day.
I just really need to wee, God.
We will pick this up later.
Cool.
- I'll meet you inside?
- Sounds good.
- Cool. See you soon.
- Okay.
- Ocupado?
- Oh, no.
No, no, out you go.
- Uh, um, I, I-
- Ah.
What time is it?
I have heard so much about you.
I have missed you.
You never know it's
going to be the last time.
Like, at the time.
I'm just...
I think this is time-travelling
tequila.
I'll trade you a line
for a shot.
I was in here with Joe,
and then he tried to kiss me,
and I freaked out,
and then he got engaged,
and then I time travelled back
to the beginning of the night.
And I think that's why I've
been given this bottle,
to stop him getting engaged.
I just have to,
I just have to get him
back into the bathroom
and kiss him again,
for real this time.
Okay, uh, just to recap,
uh, you think you can
travel through time,
and what you want to do with
that immense power is, uh,
trick someone into kissing you
and then ruin
their relationship?
Yeah.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
I'm Minnie.
So you're the single one.
- Perfect.
- Good chat.
What time is it?
I don't know.
What time do you think it is?
Geez, you don't waste any time.
Well, it's party time.
It's party time.
- Show us your tat.
- Yeah.
You look like a bag of dicks.
Sorry.
Rodney told you, didn't he?
Uh, come in, come in.
Maybe have a drink of water.
I want you to meet someone.
Guys, this is Jenny.
Jenny, this is Max, Flick,
and Minnie.
Oh, I've heard
so much about you.
Yes, well, that makes sense
'cause Joe and I have
history, right, Joe?
- Yeah.
- I told her.
And you know what?
I love that Joe is still
friends with his ex.
Yeah.
So you're an atheist?
- Anaesthetist.
- Anaesthetist, yeah.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
That must be kind of
a thankless job, right?
How do you mean?
I mean, all your patients
are asleep.
Well, yeah, but
they're awake at first.
Well, yeah, but if you
do your job right,
you just never see them again.
- Is that kind of sad?
- Yeah, totally.
So you're a, a bar chick.
Is that a difficult field
to get into?
- Mixologist?
- Yeah, it is actually,
and how'd you know that?
Oh, you know,
I just kind of got the vibe.
Thanks.
Is there a vibe?
There is a vibe for sure.
Um, so I would love
to have a chat
with you, actually,
in the bathroom
Because I, I, I need to wee,
so if you could...
Uh.
Oh, my God,
you guys know the rules.
Here we go.
♪ 'Cause there's one man and
yo, well, that's me, see ♪
♪ So let me show you 'round
while you sip your tea, G ♪
♪ But no coco loco, boom,
while I take a pee leak ♪
♪ When I hold my baby,
she say I do it nicer ♪
♪ I like my chicken
with rice and lemonade ♪
♪ And that's what you get
when she shouts out Jamboo ♪
♪ Now I got to go, yo, coco ♪
♪ Put me up, put me down, put
my feet back on the ground ♪
♪ Put me up, feel my heart
and make me happy ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, Co... ♪
Oh, the sound.
- Oh, oh.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God, are you...
- Don't don't, don't touch me.
Please don't, please.
I'm good. I just need a drink.
- No, no, you don't.
- I just need some.
Stay still, Minnie.
You want me,
like, get you some...
C-word, can you chuck
my bag, please.
Hey, then maybe just stop.
- What time is it?
- You know what time it is.
Hey.
Um, we should talk.
Yes, you know, we should,
actually.
Um, come in, come in.
No, no, no, we should
talk in the bathroom.
- The bathroom.
- Mm-hmm.
Why?
All righty then.
- Uh, let's go.
- Where's your costume?
Excuse us.
- Hey, did you bring the ice?
- No.
- No, no, no, no, no...
- No, won't be long.
Oh, but you will be long.
It's fine, Minnie.
It's fine, dude, you go.
- Yeah, now he locks it.
- Is everything okay?
Um, yeah, this will do.
- Um, hi.
- Hi.
- Joe.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- Minnie.
So you know how, um,
when it's the last time,
you never know that it's
going to be the last time
until the last time's, like,
already happened, and...
- Come on. Here we go.
- No, no, no.
Hi, Minnie.
Hi, Pia.
I didn't think you were coming.
Max is right, though.
We know you were hoping for
something more with Joe,
but he has a girlfriend now,
and she seems really cool.
Thanks, Brutus.
All we are saying is
give Jenny a chance.
Give peas a chance.
Well...
If that's the way
it's got to be.
Oh, Minnie.
What the fuck?
Oh, talk about a
"Sliding Doors" moment.
Rodney, call an ambulance.
Where is she bleeding?
No, no, no, don't move.
Don't move. The more you
move, the more you bleed.
- No, no, I got to get tequila.
- Just roll over.
- I got to get tequila.
- On your side.
Maybe don't touch her.
Maybe, don't, maybe, don't.
Okay, you can't have tequila.
You can't have anything
in your stomach
- in case they need to operate.
- Guys, guys, Minnie.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, okay.
- Stay down.
What time is it?
Minnie, you okay?
Mm-hmm.
Come in. I want you
to meet someone.
Yep.
All we're saying is give
Jenny a chance.
Okay, nice and gently this time.
Hmm, nice and gentle.
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing!?
What?
- Whoa.
- Minnie!
There we go.
- Oi.
- Shit, Minnie.
- Are you okay?
- She did that on purpose.
Yeah, she was just
smashing her face
into the glass
over and over again.
Why'd you do that?
I just really, really need
to talk to you
alone in the bathroom.
Why didn't you just ask me?
What time is it?
It's party time.
Come on.
Hey, Min, did you bring the ice?
- Go, go, go, go.
- I'm moving.
- Yeah, okay, okay.
- Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Ocupado.
Okay, what's wrong?
God, he thinks we're
going to do his coke.
We're not going to do
your coke, my God.
Well, maybe just a little bit?
Do a little bit?
Okay, whoo, okay.
Um, party time, yeah?
- Party time.
- Yeah.
Um, so, Joe, you know how, like,
uh, when, like,
when it's the last...
How you don't know
it's going to be
the last time till, like, after
it's already been the last time?
- Do you know what I'm saying?
- Not really.
And it's, like...
I've really missed you.
No, no, no, no, I can't.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I know you're
getting engaged.
God, why is this not working?
Oh, wow, you drank
all that tonight?
No, well, actually, I mean,
technically, yes,
I did, but, um,
it's complicated, anyway...
Why don't you just
have a drink with me?
Uh, no, no, I can't.
I'm allergic.
- You're allergic to tequila.
- Um, I'm an alcoholic.
Oh.
Ah, fuck, I wasn't
going to tell anyone,
um, but, well...
You know, we used
to go pretty hard.
I mean, we both
have matching tats
that say it's party time,
for fuck's sake.
And after I ruined your
engagement to Cameron,
when I got to New York,
I kind of kept going...
Like, really hard.
Wound up on the floor,
face down, convulsing,
and pissed myself.
- Oh.
- Yeah...
So I've been sober
for three months now.
Look, I'm not blaming you.
I'm just trying to, uh, take
responsibility for myself.
So I am, I am sorry.
Oh, it's, it's not your fault.
No, I knew what I was doing.
Yeah but like, he was
kind of a dickhead.
Like, we never should have
been engaged
in the first place, honestly.
Wait, how'd you know I,
I was getting engaged?
I didn't even tell you
I had a girlfriend.
That's true, um...
Her name's Jenny, and she's
actually not a bartender,
she's a mixologist.
Uh, and you are planning to
propose to her at midnight
with a ring that you
have in your left sock.
- Right sock.
- Whatever.
Seriously,
I, I, I'm freaking out.
How, how do you know that?
Yeah, um,
so since we're sharing...
This is a bottle of
time-travelling tequila,
and I think, I think the reason
I've been given this tequila
is to stop you proposing.
So Rodney told you.
No, no, no, he didn't.
He didn't.
God, I don't,
I really don't know how
to prove this to you.
Just, um, take a shot with me.
Yeah, that's what we'll do.
Just let's have a drink
together, and you'll understand.
Are you listening?
Minnie, I just told you
I'm an alcoholic, so...
Okay, are you listening to me?
This is not even alcohol.
This is, like...
- Right.
- Special, special stuff.
Trust me. Just have some.
- Minnie, don't.
- Just have, just...
Please, just don't do that.
Joe, listen. If I'm wrong,
I'm wrong, but...
What is wrong with you?
I just told you
I'm an alcoholic.
You're trying to pour
booze down my throat.
That's fucked up.
Even for you,
that's really fucked up.
We doing shots?
Geez, you don't waste any time.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, it's just
been a really big night.
It's like, 9 o'clock.
Long shift.
Do you want to come in
and lie down or?
Yeah, actually,
that's a really good idea.
Yeah? Yeah.
We can catch up after.
Sorry it took ages.
Pump was in the bathroom.
Bathroom was ocupado.
I mean,
I shouldn't be surprised.
C-word brought cocaine
to Ria's birthday party.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah, I know.
A bit funny looking when they
first come out, aren't they?
Yeah, she has my eyes.
I hope she doesn't
get my chin hair.
Um...
Seems like you're,
you're really loving
motherhood now, though.
Yeah.
I bet Rodney's useless, eh?
Oh, not to her, he's not.
You know, Minnie, it's funny.
I used to,
I used to have a job.
I used to love going to work.
People used to look up to me.
And I used to party,
and I used to have fun.
And now I'm just anxious
all the time.
I'm so sorry I just...
don't really have anyone
to talk to anymore.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
If it makes you feel any better.
All I do is work.
- Hmm.
- I don't really have any...
kind of life outside of that,
so...
And today,
I had to watch Cameron
have a baby.
Who's Cameron?
We were engaged.
Now he's a dad,
to a little baby girl.
I always wanted a girl.
Well, you can have Ria
on Thursdays.
I really want to start
aerobics again,
- and that's what...
- No, that's okay.
He was never really
the one anyway.
I guess what I'm saying
is just that,
you know...
You and Rodney are just like,
really lucky.
I think you should nap now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just, just a little one though,
okay?
Please wake me up
before midnight, yeah?
Totally going to wake you up.
Yeah, okay.
Thank you.
Don't forget!
No.
Three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
No, seriously,
what is wrong with you?
I don't know,
I thought you'd be happy.
Like, you're right.
It was just a joke.
Hey!
You didn't wake me up.
Sorry, you just looked
so peaceful.
Don't worry,
you didn't miss much.
It's a yes?
- Yes, of course.
- Yes?
Yay! This is mad.
Guys.
Show them, show them quick.
Oh, Minnie, Minnie,
you have to meet my girl...
No, fiancée.
This is, this is Jenny.
Jenny, Minnie.
Minnie, Jenny.
Champagne?
Let's celebrate.
No, I'm okay, thank you.
Jenny, why aren't you drinking?
I, um...
I'm not drinking tonight
because...
- He's an alcoholic.
- I'm pregnant.
We're having a baby.
Oh, congratulations, Jenny.
That's really good news.
- Thank you.
- Hey, brother.
- Congratulations.
- I'm so excited.
- That's so beautiful.
- Yes.
Let's get a photo of you three.
- Sure.
- Sorry,
what the fuck is wrong with you?
You knew that you
were going to propose
to your pregnant girlfriend
and you still tried to
kiss me in the bathroom.
Ah, what?
Minnie,
I saw you at the door
for two seconds.
No seriously I, I just, I dunno.
I dunno what
she's talking about.
It's okay, it's okay.
You warned me
she might be like this.
Sorry, like what?
Jesus, just stop.
He moved to the
other side of the world
to get away from you.
Is that true?
Yeah, we're bad. We're bad
for each other Minnie.
We both know that.
This is so unfair.
This is so fucking unfair.
You're going to have a baby?
And Cameron had a baby
and it's like,
where's my fucking baby?
You know, like,
who's going to get
my apple juice?
Minnie, maybe you should
go back to sleep.
No, actually, maybe you
should have woken me up
when you said you would, Pia.
Minnie, I think Pia's right?
Oh, shocking.
Flick taking anybody's side,
but mine.
She always takes
your side actually,
no matter what crazy shit...
Not since you came along,
home wrecker.
It's my house!
Alright, why don't we maybe
just all just try to relax.
- Yeah.
- Oh, should we relax, Rodney?
Should we just like, forget
how we're feeling and relax?
How's that working out
for you in your marriage?
Pretty good?
And he's got cocaine.
I'm going home.
Can I have your car keys?
No.
Can I please have your car keys?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Shit.
- Evening, Miss.
- Hi.
Just one long,
continuous breath, please.
Whoa.
Never seen that before.
I reckon this might have
something to do with it.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
you can't take that actually.
No, I need that.
I really need that.
I don't think you do, love.
No, seriously.
I'm not even drunk.
I'm not even drunk,
it doesn't even affect me.
I feel totally fine.
Just...
Just let me have one more shot
and then you can
arrest me, okay?
Righto.
Out you hop.
Orina del Diablo.
She's shit faced.
I'm surprised
she's still on the road.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Give me the tequila.
Put the gun down, now!
Look, there's a safety,
you've got to...
Thank you.
What? You want to help
her aim it?
Whoa!
God!
Okay.
Put your gun down.
How many times have I told
you to button your holster?
Good, tequila now, thank you.
Now! Come on.
Thank you.
You okay, buddy?
Just a sec.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no!
Jesus.
You could have killed me.
Hey, Flick?
Can I have your keys please?
Um, yeah, sure.
- Thank you.
- Unlocked still, though.
- Okay.
- I thought she needed to wee?
You want to play silly buggers,
do ya?
♪ Sunshine ♪
Call for back up.
♪ On the window
makes me happy ♪
♪ Like I should be ♪
Fuck!
♪ Really sleazy ♪
♪ Then it hits me ♪
♪ Don't tell me ♪
♪ You can see
what it means to me ♪
♪ Leave me
Don't tell me ♪
♪ You can see ♪
Oh, you like that, do ya?
- Get out of the car.
- Miss?
You need to get out of the car.
Lady! Out of the car.
Open the door.
Open the door to the car.
You fucking little arsehole!
Why won't you let me leave?
- What time is it?
- Oh, fuck off.
You, okay?
What's her problem?
She's in a bit of a mood.
Yeah, we're kicking her out.
She also saw Cameron have
a baby at the hospital today.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Ah, Minnie,
did she bring the ice?
What is she doing?
Our savings.
Our what?
Minnie!
Minnie, stop!
What are you doing?
Oh, ocupado.
Let's do this.
Oh, my stars.
- Alright, you ready?
- Yes.
Here we go.
Just so you know,
I can't wear a condom.
- They hurt too much.
- Oh, poor baby.
- Good?
- Yeah, just gimme a sec.
- Sure?
- It's all good.
- No, take the time.
- It's fine.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Yep?
- Okay.
- Alright, cool.
- Okay, alright. Here we go.
- You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- No, no, not like that.
- No?
Mm-mm.
Just... No...
Hang on, hang on, stop.
Stop, you got to, got to...
Just a sec.
- Ah, ah yeah.
- No, no.
Yeah, yeah.
- I'm Karl, by the way.
- Cool.
- Rodney and I share an office.
- I don't care.
- Okay.
Good.
Come on...
Happy New Year.
Alright, out you hop.
- Thank you.
- You're so welcome.
Wow.
What's that?
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
Stop it! No, no.
- I don't want kids.
- Okay. Alright, alright.
At all! I don't even know
who you are.
Jesus Christ, calm down.
How old are you?
None of your business.
Forty?
Thirty six!
Only asking 'cause if
you're really that desperate,
they're running an egg
freezing trial at my hospital,
and I know that they could
do with a few more geriatrics
in the program me.
Geriatrics?
Oh, you know, 35 and over.
Jesus Christ.
Well, I'm not desperate,
I just...
Momentary lapse in judgement,
I guess.
Yeah, hey, I get it.
Single girl -
late thirties...
Mid thirties, thanks.
You've got to meet someone,
fall in love and then,
even thinking about
having a kid - that's what?
Two to three years at least,
and that puts you 40-ish plus,
giving birth.
Yeah so, it's possible.
Hey, I don't make the rules.
I'm just saying, it's harder.
Plus, you know,
I've never met a kid
who was worth burning down
a man's favourite pub.
How am I doing?
Any notes?
Stop.
Minnie.
What are you doing?
Yeah, not much,
keeping busy, you?
Minnie, what the fuck
is wrong with you?
Whoa, Rodney, chill.
It's okay.
I'm just having some fun.
You'll get your money back,
don't worry about it.
Where'd you get
that bottle of tequila?
This is mezcal, actually,
No, seriously,
where'd you get it?
Gimme the bottle, Minnie.
You need help, Minnie.
- Just give it to me.
- Absolutely not.
No way!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Joe.
- Okay.
- Joe.
No, it's fine.
Alright, Joe,
just give me the...
I'll do you one better.
- No!
- No, no, no.
What the fuck is
wrong with you both?
Oh my God.
Hey, hey?
Oh my God,
call an ambulance, Rodney!
- No, no Minnie, Minnie don't.
- Joe, give me that bottle.
- No, no, no.
- Joe, gimme the fucking...
Don't give it to her,
Minnie! Minnie don't.
Don't give it to her!
Minnie, don't.
No!
No, no, no.
Minnie, don't!
No, no!
Okay.
Minnie, what the fuck?
- Minnie?
- What is happening?
I got mine in Mexico,
where did you get yours?
Flick brought it back
for me from Mexico.
I went back so many
times trying to find more.
Wait, is that how you
learned to speak Spanish?
Yeah.
Ah...
When did you start drinking?
Tonight.
When did you start
drinking yours?
Mexico. 1989.
I had one shot back there
and I just thought
it was the mushrooms,
and then one night
I was home in Melbourne -
I did a shot and
I was back in Mexico.
I freaked out.
I didn't touch it again
for years.
Years?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know, I, er...
I failed my exams and,
things weren't going so well
- and so I...
- Shh, shh, shh...
Sorry...
You...
You failed?
Yeah.
You're a surgeon.
You, you topped the year.
Eventually, yeah.
You cheated.
- I didn't cheat.
- You absolutely cheated.
I came second in our year
because you fucking cheated!
Whoa, I did just as much
work as you guys.
In fact, actually, like I did
like five times as much work.
- Five times?
- Yeah.
- You got to do it five times?
That actually makes so much
more sense to me now.
How's that?
That's how you have all of this.
When did you stop?
When Pia got pregnant.
I couldn't risk
losing the baby and,
I was already down
to my last shot.
But every now and again, I do
like to give it a little sniff.
It's Mexico man,
it's too hot for a jumper.
Rodney, Flick, this one
I'm dedicating to you...
♪ One summer
I'll find a way ♪
will always remain ♪
Rodney,
put your clothes back on.
No, this is how I live now.
No, no, no.
I don't want to flush ten years
down the drain.
Sorry, that just
sounded really...
- really nice.
- Yeah.
I mean, not,
Joe's guitar playing.
Definitely should have taught
him more than four chords but...
I really wish that I came
on that trip with you guys.
I've been
doing this a bit lately.
Life was just so much
simpler before Ria.
What happened here?
Mm. One of our weddings
got a little out of control.
One of?
How far into the future
have you gone?
About 10 past midnight.
You drank all that tonight?
Yeah.
Yeah, well I was...
I was trying to fix things.
Y2K?
- Don't tell me Pia is right.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, it's, um...
Hey, in all of your shots, like
all the different timelines.
Did Joe and I
ever end up together?
Yeah, yeah.
Um, yeah, big house, three
beautiful children there was...
- Really?
- Yeah.
No mate, no.
Sorry.
Alright, alright,
alright. Ten!
Nine, eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three, two,
one.
- Happy new year!
- No, mate.
It's happening.
No. It's nothing.
It's just Rodney.
- Rodney?
- Rodney!
It's the end of the world!
Ah, it's a joke.
You were in on this?
Me? No.
- You all were in on this?
- No, I wasn't.
- Me, no.
- No.
So humiliating
Pia, it's just a joke, sorry.
Why does everything
have to be a joke?
You know, I might not
have a job after this.
There's still going to be
computers in the year 2000.
Great, because I don't
want to be stuck here
taking care of our kid
all the time.
It's fucking killing me.
I am going to my mum's.
Hey, whoa, Pia,
you can't drive like that.
Watch me.
Pia, stop.
Hey, hey.
Pia, Pia!
Hey...
Unlock the door.
You're overreacting.
Jesus Christ.
Dude, what the hell
happened to you two?
Minnie!
You have to help.
It's okay, the cops are
just up the road.
They're going to stop her
before anything happens.
- Don't worry about it.
- No, she's going to leave me.
I need to fix it.
Okay.
What do you mean?
I need to fix it.
Mate!
I have two shots left.
- Okay.
- Okay?
I can do it better.
I can be better.
Mate, you are so lucky
that I love you.
Right, you owe me, okay.
Not that you're ever
going to remember.
Whoa, hey, hey, wait.
We both need to do one.
- What do you mean?
- I don't want to be left here.
I mean, is that how it works?
I disappear and you
stay here or what?
I don't know, I've never
been left behind before.
I don't really want to find out,
you know?
You want me to finish my bottle?
You want my last shot?
Okay.
Just go get a shot glass, okay?
But we can use the -
the lid's a shot glass.
Is it?
That's good to know.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Alright, um...
- Three, two...
- Wait, um...
Sorry, is it on one or
three, two, one, go at three?
Fucking go!
What time is it?
Rodney told you, didn't he?
Yeah, he did.
Alrighty then!
Where's your costume?
Didn't have time.
- Is that yours?
- Yep.
Come in. I want to
introduce you to someone.
Yeah.
Hey, Min.
Good one.
I am buzzing.
I forgot about that weird
tingling sensation on re-entry.
Yeah. Okay, okay...
Just, can you..
- Right?
- Right.
You okay?
You know, I just,
every time I restart,
I really need to wee
but C-word's always
in the bathroom.
Oh.
Just use the en suite.
En suite. Cool.
Ocupado.
Minnie, I'm so glad you came.
I didn't think you were coming.
We missed you at the birthday.
Hey, do you want a Sea Breeze?
- They just need some...
- Ice!
Shit, I forgot the ice.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not okay.
Flick, can I please
have your car keys?
Ah...
Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
- It's okay...
No, no, no. I got it.
Just the ice, thanks.
Got the ice.
Hey!
- Sea Breeze?
- Yes, please.
Hey, hey, um...
The lights thing, at midnight.
Alright. Okay.
Okay, I'm just all about
having fun this time.
- Great.
- Yeah.
Just like we used to.
Hey, Pia?
Hey!
Did you do that deliberately?
That wasn't an accident,
though...
Alright, nah...
Hey, come here. Come here,
come here, come here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, um...
Pull your head in,
you are wasted.
- No, I'm good.
- No, not good, not good...
You're not good, okay?
We can't redo this, alright?
So just..
I'll go have a shower.
Alright Rodney, do not
take your clothes off!
Don't say it.
Save it for midnight.
Pia...
I'm going to have a shower.
Care to join?
- Oh, no. Rodney!
- Alright, up you get.
That'll do.
- Hop up.
- It's good. It's alright.
I just need to iron
the creases out.
Anyone got some gear?
Karl?
- Huh, don't hold out on me.
- Hey, hey, hey...
Don't...
Hey, Rodney.
Jesus, what the fuck is
wrong with you people?
It's a fucking party!
Look it up.
- Whatever. Fuck off.
- Hey, hey.
We got time travelling
tequila, so later losers.
We don't have any of that time
travelling tequila left, mate.
No, we'll have the worm.
No, we're not going
to eat the worm.
We don't know what happens
if we eat the worm.
- You don't want to eat...
- Stop, Rodney. Stop!
- Oi!
- Stop it. Stop it.
- Rodney!
- Stop.
Stop! Stop.
Chill.
- I'm going to go lay down.
- Good idea.
See you later.
It could have been worse.
Hey!
Stop.
You can't just erase 10 years
of your life. What about Ria?
I'll still have her.
This time,
we'll be a better prepared.
You'd have to conceive
at the exact same moment.
Same sperm, same egg.
I couldn't even recreate
a kiss tonight.
So we'll have a different baby.
What the fuck?
You want to throw it all away
just so that you can do it
one more time, but better.
What about Pia?
She'll never know.
Yeah, but you'll know.
I did everything for her
and she's miserable.
I'm miserable.
You've got a family
who loves you.
I know it's really hard
right now,
but it's going to get better,
okay?
Nuh! Huh-uh.
Nah!
What do I know,
I just work in IT.
I mean seriously,
what is wrong with you.
It's fucking killing me
I wasn't going to do it.
I was never going to do it.
Uh...
What happened in here?
It's no big deal.
I mean, who can blame him?
He's not coping, I'm not coping.
I'm glad he's got his
friends here, though.
Do you want to go back
to the lounge?
Come on.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Fuck!
I'll get the ice!
I think it's stopped bleeding.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Oh, mate.
- It's pretty bad.
- Headache.
Yeah, I bet.
Here we go. You ready?
Yep. Okay.
Ice, ice, baby.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
Let's go.
Ow.
The glass in that door
is so clean.
Is Rodney okay, is he..
Yeah, yeah, he's fine.
He just needs to sleep it off.
It's like old times.
Yeah.
Hey, are you pissed about,
um, Jenny?
No, of course not.
I think that..
I think she's perfect for you,
actually.
I mean, you're clearly
punching above your weight.
Oh, yeah.
You seem different.
Yeah, I feel different.
Hey, I'm going to propose.
Oh, well, I'm flattered, mate,
but no, thank you.
No, um...
Jenny is pregnant.
Congratulations.
I think you're going
to be a great dad.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You know, I always
thought it would be you.
- Oh, don't say that.
- Oh, sorry.
I don't think you mean that.
I mean, am I..
Am I making a huge mistake or...
No, you're not.
You're going to be great.
I think you're ready.
And I think that the tatts
have aged really poorly
and we should probably
get them removed.
Yeah. Party time's over.
Yeah, party time's over.
Oh, shit.
- Nostrovia.
- Wait, wait.
I can't believe you kissed her.
You been drinking?
- No, no.
- Are you sure?
Yeah.
So, you did that sober?
What's going on?
Yeah, Joe, why don't you tell
everyone what's going on?
Look, me and Minnie...
Minnie and I, kissed.
- Oh.
- Jesus, Minnie.
Yeah, but like barely.
I mean, it was...
It was a goodbye kiss.
It was nothing.
- Completely.
- Trust me.
Like, why would you
invite me here?
Why would you ask me to spend
the holidays with your family
and all of your friends?
And then why would you kiss
the person that you moved
to the other side of the
world to get away from?
I am sorry. If I could take
it back, I would, but I can't.
I can.
I think.
Um..
I think I can.
This is going to sound
pretty insane, but...
Oi, here we go.
There is one minute to midnight.
I have a bottle of
time travelling tequila.
Here we go.
Mescal. If it has a worm
in it, it's mescal.
Anyway, I think
if I eat the worm,
it's going to send me
back in time
and then I can just
fix all of this.
So...
Okay, I have no fucking idea
what's going on.
See you on the other side.
Hopefully.
Yeah, you've just got to
give it a big tap on the...
There you go.
Is it alive?
Eat it.
No, actually.
No.
Fuck that.
Yeah, no, not...
not this time, um...
I'm sorry, Jenny.
My life is just not where I
thought it would be right now,
and I think I thought that
maybe Joe would fix things,
but actually, Joe and I
have always just been
each other's backup plan,
haven't we?
And now he doesn't need
a backup plan,
'cause he's got the real deal.
He's got you, so...
It's true.
Hey...
Oh, no.
- Don't do that.
- I love you.
I know. I love you, too,
but just get up.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Nope...
- No, don't...
Hey.
Should I? No?
No, Minnie, I reckon they need
to sort it out themselves.
Yep.
Phew. Sorry for ruining
everyone's night.
- You didn't ruin it.
- Well, she kind of has.
No.
No, she hasn't. She hasn't.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Guys.
It's happened.
Happy New Year.
Oh. Happy New Year.
See, nothing happened.
Millennium.
Whoo! Whoo-hoo!
- I'm so sorry.
- That was really stupid.
Minnie, come on!
♪ Walk out into velvet ♪
♪ Nothing more to say ♪
♪ You're my favourite... ♪
It's the end of the world!
♪ You're my Saturday ♪
♪ 'Cause you're my number one ♪
♪ I'm like a dog to get you ♪
♪ I want it up and on ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Sunset only seconds ♪
♪ Just ripe, then it's gone ♪
♪ Got no new intentions ♪
♪ Just right, then it's gone ♪
♪ 'Cause you're my number one ♪
♪ I'm like a dog to get you ♪
♪ I want it up and on ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ I'll be there to meet you ♪
- Nice to meet you.
Okay, you need to practise,
mate.
Ready? Yeah, come on.
Give her a hold. Come on.
Wait, how do I do it?
That's okay.
Daddy's coming.
Daddy's going to come
and save you.
- Well done!
- Hello.
- Hello...
- Alright, alright.
Step out of the way, amateur.
You'll get the hang of it, mate.
That's better.
♪ 'Cause you're my number one ♪
♪ I'm like a dog to get you ♪
♪ I want it up and on ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Hey guys, I've got
something for you.
What?
I think that it's time.
Do you even have
anywhere else to go?
I mean, you're coming
in our car, right?
What about all your shit?
Yeah okay, well look, I didn't
think it through that well, but
it's the gesture, right?
We appreciate the gesture.
Maybe you should take this back.
Alrighty.
Just for a bit, Max.
What is wrong with you?
Sorry, mate.
We're not going to
leave her on the street.
She's going to
live with us forever.
♪ What's goin' on... ♪
♪ I can't wait 'til ♪
♪ One summer ♪
♪ I'll find a way ♪
♪ One summer,
always remain ♪
remember the way ♪
♪ One summer,
never the same ♪
We should start a band.
That's, better than I remember.
♪ Started out last night, I was
thinkin' of days gone by ♪
♪ Of the times I've had ♪
♪ And the things that
I've left behind ♪
♪ Some change, some die,
still we manage to survive ♪
♪ It's knowin' when and
what to do, it's up to you ♪
♪ Don't know what's goin' on
I can't wait 'til, wait 'til ♪
♪ One summer,
I'll find a way ♪
will always remain ♪
♪ One summer,
remember the way ♪